sunclassifiedads.com 2016-11-24

# Sun Classified Ads | Privacy Policy | Post Free Classifieds | Classified Ad Sites

Protecting your privacy:

Feel comfortable using our web sites.  
Feel secure submitting information to us.  
Contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site.  
Know that by using our sites you are consenting to the collection of certain data

Sun Classified Ads Classifieds collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site.

HOW'S THE INFORMATION USED?  
We use personal information to:

    * Help us provide personalized features  
    * Tailor our sites to your interest  
    * Get in touch with you when necessary 

The primary goal of Sun Classified Ads Classifieds in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout Sun Classified Ads Classifieds. 

When you are asked for personal information on Sun Classified Ads Classifieds, you are sharing that information with "Sun Classified Ads" Classifieds alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of "Sun Classified Ads" Classifieds. For example, when you enter personal information on the ad posting form, this information will generally be included in your ad, unless specifically stated otherwise. 

With whom your information may be shared:

Other than information displayed as part of your profile, as a general rule, "Sun Classified Ads" Classifieds will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.

Policy Updates:

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

International Users:

By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of "Sun Classified Ads" we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.
